Daria Mikita

Whistler BC (672) 515-9430 nauticalstars21@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

As a bilingual IT specialist with over 10 years of experience in dynamic sales, service organization and more than 20 years of experience in software troubleshooting background in Mac applications and possess a confident and solid approach to software installation, configuration and diagnostics.

SKILLS

- Strong Organizational Skills
- Confidentiality and Data Protection
- Research and Analytical Skills
- Client Management
- Supply Inventory Control
- Document and File Management
- Remote Conferencing

- Website Management
- Directory Maintenance
- Multilingual in French, English, Spanish and Polish
- Complex Data Interpretation
- Electronic Records Management
- Process Optimization

WORK HISTORY

BILINGUAL SENIOR APPLE CERTIFIED TECHNICIAN AND MANAGER | 12/2014 to Current Burnt Stew Computer Solutions - Whistler, BC

- Sales and servicing of all Apple products north of Vancouver
- Teaching customers how to use their devices, together and efficiently
- Inventory management of Apple accessories and 3rd party accessories
- Premium Service Provider status for 2016, 2017 and 2018
- Community instructor Intro to iCloud part 1 and 2 classes
- GSX Admin
- Server administrator, set-up, installation (configuration) and maintaining the Diagnostics server
- Maintaining a high percentage of first fixed rate and customer satisfaction scores throughout the year
- Lightspeed migration and administration setup
- WordPress maintenance
- Google Workspace admininistration and migration
- Domain registration and setup

BILINGUAL ACCOUNT AND IT ADMINISTRATOR | 09/2011 to 05/2014 SodaStream Canada LTD - Winnipeg, MB

- Maintained data and orders in Microsoft Navision
- LAN and PC network setup and migration
- Google Workspace administration and user management
- Bilingual product label translation and regulatory compliance
- Adobe Illustrator basics
- Bilingual customer service and troubleshooting on email and telephone
- Employee device management
- Website product management

BILINGUAL ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT AND IT SUPPORT | 05/2009 to 09/2011 Eco Stream Canada - Winnipeg, MB

- Managed large orders from major clients and maintained ensuring website inventory
- Interacted with vendors, contractors, and professional services personnel to receive orders, direct activities, and communicated instructions.
- Shipped and received products on large-scale orders
- Website inventory maintenance
- Employee computer user setup and maintenance
- Microsoft Navision inventory management

EDUCATION

She Codes Academy - Online | Front End Developer Expected in 09/2023

Coursera - Online | Google Apps Admin Fundamentals 2018

Apple ATLAS - Online | Apple Product Professional 2016

Apple ATLAS - Online | Apple Certified iOS Technician 2016

Witz Education - Toronto, ON | Apple Certified Macintosh Technician 2014

Witz Education - Toronto, ON | Apple Certified Support Professional 10.9 2013

St. Boniface University - Winnipeg, MB | Bachelor's Degree Anthropology, 2011